这些就是你上周错过故事
This is what you missed last week on Shameless.
我亲爱的！
My baby!
真爱
True love.
hey 帅哥
Hey, hot stuff.
-你干嘛的
-做房地产的 我住在迈阿密
What do you do?
Real estate. I live in Miami.
-我把lip轰走了
-他去哪里了
I kicked Lip out.
Where'd he go?
我今天晚上能在这里过夜么
Is it all right if
I stay over tonight?
-看见jimmy不奇怪么
-谁是jimmy
Was it weird seeing Jimmy?
Who's Jimmy?
jimmy就是steve
Jimmy is Steve.
妈的 我这个礼拜五就能看见这个小家伙了么
Holy shit. I'm gonna see
the little guy on Friday?
是的 很快的
Yep. For, like, a second.
草他妈的 这个臭鸡巴快折磨死我了
Christ almighty!
This cocksucker's killing me!
当他们正常的时候 他们在一次显得很正常
When they're good, they're good.
你是唯一一个真正了解我的人
You're the only one
who truly understands me.
她出什么问题了么 她已经好几天没下床了
Is something wrong with her?
She hasn't gotten out of bed in days.
monica有精神病 ，debs
Monica's bipolar, Debs.
你是该吃药了 是不
Time for you to
go back on your meds, huh?
-我勒个去
-怎么了
Holy fuck.
CARL: What happened?
-老妈 老妈
-天啊 这儿有一起事故
Mommy, Mommy...
Oh, God, there's been an accident.
-她在大出血 他们正在路上
-你和我一起么
She's bleeding badly. They're on their way.
You with me?
-一切都会好的 我们没事儿
-我和你在一起
It's gonna be okay. We're good,
we're good. Stay with me.
-她怎么样了
-她已经稳定了
How is she?
She's stable.
你应该回家
DOCTOR:
You should go home.
-lip刚打给我
-他要来么
Lip just called.
He's coming?
-=karen在楼上生孩子
-我滴个天
Karen's having a baby upstairs.
Holy fuck!
要生了 要生了
It's coming, it's coming!
他有什么毛病么
What's wrong with him?
-他有唐氏综合症 debs
-你他妈的搞什么 karen
He's has Downs Syndrome, Debs.
What the fuck, Karen?
我从来没说过它是你的孩子
I never said it was your baby.
我得到孩子了
SHEILA:
I got the baby, I got the baby!
快点 快点
JODY:
Come on, come on!
太好了 我得到孩子了
Whoo!
I've got a baby!
【贴吧无耻之徒字幕组】
【翻译】折翼的鸟 NG 郭巍 oh ba ttle
【校对】dream NG 郭威 哎呦
♪ Think of all the luck
you got ♪
♪ Know that it's not
for naught ♪
♪ You were beaming once before ♪
♪ But it's not like that
anymore ♪
♪ What is this downside ♪
♪ That you speak of? ♪
♪ What is this feeling ♪
♪ You're so sure of? ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Round up the friends you got ♪
♪ Know that they're not
for naught ♪
♪ You were willing once before ♪
♪ But it's not like that
anymore ♪
♪ What is this downside ♪
♪ That you speak of? ♪
♪ What is this feeling ♪
♪ You're so... ♪
♪ Sure of? ♪
Monica!
Monica?
Monica Jean Kallagher!
Monica!
我的天啊
Oh, God.
妈的
Oh, shit.
我的天啊
Oh, God...
老天
Jesus.
死纳粹
Schutzstaffen.
你他妈的在做什么
What the hell are you doing?
你偷走了我的妻子
You stole my wife!
什么
What?
你偷走了我的妻子 我想让她回到我身边
You stole my wife,
and I want her back.
好吧 探访时间是九点到四点
Okay, visiting hours
are 9:00 to 4:00.
你那个时间再来看她吧
You want to see her,
come back then.
-出来 monica
-别乱叫
Come out, Monica!
Hey!
赶紧出来
Get out of here.
monica 跟我回家
Monica, come home!
我爱你
I love you!
我永远都不会离开你
I'll never leave you!
永远不会
Never...
你是一个天使
SHEILA:
You're an angel.
是上帝的恩赐
A blessing.
感谢老天赐给我们一个亚洲小BB
My little Kung Pow blessing.
得弄明白怎么把这个跟踪的东西弄掉
Hmm. Gotta figure out how to
get this security thing off.
你是一个多么可爱，美丽，
What a big, beautiful,
像可爱的维尼熊一样的男孩儿啊
panda-Pooh Bear boy you are.
快看
Oh, look.
他的小鸡鸡上有一层皮
He's still got his
little dingy-ding skin.
我们应该给他割包皮么
Should we get him circumcised?
当然不 顺其自然吧
Hell, no.
Let that extra derma ride.
他需要一个名字
Oh, he needs a name.
hiram怎么样 我老爸的名字
What about Hiram,
for my father?
你是hymmie么
Are you a Hymmie?
我觉得他们能追踪这个东西 就像一个婴儿找回系统是么
Hmm. Think they can track
this thing, like a baby LoJack?
你是小hymmie么
Are you a little Hymmie?
你是小hymmie维尼熊么 他应该有个中国式的名字
A Hymmie-wymie?
The name should be something Chinese.
让他和他的民族保持某种联系
Keep him connected to his people.
Hmm.
中国式的
Chinese...
陈
Chen, Chan,
常
Chang...
王
Wing? Wang?
太紧了
Wu?
Hm... it's pretty tight.
我可不想手一滑 把他脚给割了
I don't want to slip
and cut his leg off.
好吧 你可以把他脚环
Well, you could
clip his ankle bracelet
和包皮一起割了
and his foreskin
at the same time.
我的朋友cindy回去工作了
Hey, my friend Cindy
went back to work.
为了生活 不得不啊
Has to pump.
For a five-spot,
我打赌他就能帮我们找到母乳
I bet she'd hook us up
with some breast milk.
他们正在找他
They're going to
be looking for him.
-我们需要把他藏起来
-藏到阁楼里怎么样
We need to hide him.
How about the attic?
就像那部关于希伯来女孩的电影一样
Like that movie about
the Hebrew girl.
不行 那里冬天会很冷
地下室怎么样
No, it gets cold in the winter.
What about the basement?
不行 亲爱的 那里会是他们首先查看的地方
No, it's the first place
they'll look, sweetie.
烘干机里呢
Dryer?
但是不能忘了他在那里
Just can't forget he's in there.
恩
Right.
我来清理桌子
I'll clear the table.
debs上床睡觉吧
Debs, bedtime.
妈的
Fuck.
我的天啊
Oh, Jesus.
这些可怜的孩子
These poor kids.
不要担心 他们原本已经被搞的一塌糊涂了
Don't worry, they're already
pretty fucked up.
我的意思
I mean...
好的 你可以呼吸的
Okay, you can breathe.
Ah!
大口的呼吸
MAN:
Keep breathing.
你会没事儿的 对么
You gonna be all right?
F 我
Fiona, I...
我早该看清
♪ I should know ♪
自己到底是谁
♪ Who I am by now ♪
我徒步前行
♪ I walk ♪
唱片不知为何停止
♪ The record stands somehow ♪
想起了那个冬天
♪ Thinking of winter ♪
你的名字就像是碎片一样融入我的身体
♪ Your name is the splinter inside me ♪
当我开始等待
♪ While I wait ♪
我始终记得 那个九月
♪ And I remember the sound ♪
你在闹区的音容相貌
♪ Of your November downtown ♪
我始终记得
♪ And I remember the truth ♪
和你在一起的十月是多么的真实
♪ A warm December with you ♪
但是我没有必要做出这个错误的决定
♪ But I don't have to make this mistake ♪
我不需要一直让自己备受煎熬
♪ And I don't have to stay this way ♪
要是我会等待
♪ If only I would wait ♪
现在 关于我们所有的回忆都应清楚的浮现
♪ The walk has all been cleared by now ♪
你的声音会一直出现在我的脑海中
♪ Your voice is all I hear somehow ♪
调出那个冬天的记忆
♪ Calling out, winter ♪
你的声音是我身体的一个碎片
♪ Your voice is the splinte inside me ♪
当我开始等待
♪ While I wait ♪
Fiona?
我记得那个声音
♪ I remember the sound ♪
我在 进来吧
Yeah, come on in.
你没睡么
You awake?
是的
Yeah.
我始终记得
♪ And I remember the truth ♪
和你在一起的十月是多么的真实
♪ A warm December with you ♪
但是我没有必要做出这个错误的决定
♪ But I don't have to make this mistake ♪
我不需要一直让自己备受煎熬
♪ And I don't have to stay this way ♪
要是我会等待
♪ If only I would wait ♪
我可能早就已经迷失了自我
♪ I could have lost myself in rough ♪
没关系
Shh. It's okay.
一切都会好起来的
It's gonna be okay.
我始终记得 那个九月
♪ I remember the sound ♪
你在闹区的音容相貌
♪ Of your November downtown... ♪
有人把孩子偷走了
Somebody stole the baby.
他们认为那是我母亲干的
They think it was my mom.
天啊
Jesus.
你报警了么
You call the police?
和往常一样 她可能只是被吓坏了
She probably just
freaked out, like always.
我要将宝宝拿回来
I'm gonna get it back.
恩 或许 你应该让你的母亲看着孩子一阵子
Well, maybe you should let
your mom keep him for awhile.
你知道 至少直到你确定
You know, at least till you're sure
你不会再改变主意
you're not gonna change your mind.
我不会改变主意的
I'm not gonna change my mind.
但以后的谁知道呢 你可能真的
Yeah, but you don't know that.
I mean, you could really...
我不想再靠近那玩意儿 知道了么
I don't want that fucking
thing anywhere near me, okay?
去问问别人我什么时候能他妈的出院
Go ask somebody when I can
get the hell out of here.
我得趁温迪快餐停止供应早餐之前赶紧去
I want to hit Wendy's before
they stop serving breakfast.
早安
Morning.
孩子们还在睡么
Kids still sleeping?
是的
Uh, yeah.
火鸡和鸡蛋么
Turkey and eggs?
上面加了蘑菇 土豆和煎饼
With mashed potato pancakes
还有果冻
and cranberry jelly.
Hmm.
你已经可以做一个合法的居民在这儿晃悠了么 steve
You back to being a legal
resident around here, Steve?
他现在叫jimmy
Jimmy. His name's
Jimmy now.
steve是他用来骗我
Steve was just an alias he used
不让我知道他真实身份的别名
to lie to me about
who he really was.
一点都不酷 jimmy -steve
Ooh, not cool, Jimmy-Steve.
-鸡蛋
-加点
Eggs?
To go.
我改名字是因为我偷车的缘故
I changed my name 'cause I was
如果被发现了
stealing cars.
Didn't want anyone to
不想让任何人追踪到我
be able to track me down
if things went south.
和你没有任何的关系
It didn't have anything
to do with you.
好吧
Yeah.
我想要见见你的家人
I want to meet your family.
oh 不 你不能
Oh, no, you don't.
是的 我会去
Yes, I do.
他们是十分的讨厌人
They're miserable people.
卑鄙  极端利己 一群白痴
Nasty, egomaniacal
shit-heads.
所有人么
好吧 当我的母亲喝多酒的时候
All of them?
Yeah, Mom's okay
她看起来还算正常
when she's knocked back
enough Chardonnay.
你们家里有多少人啊
How many of you are there?
母亲 父亲---白痴明星
Uh, Mom, Dad--
shit-head superstar.
老哥-
Older brother Chip--
被训练过的白痴明星
shit-head
superstar-in-training.
我已经迫不及待的想要见他们了
Can't wait to meet them.
你一定会失望的
You're going to
be disappointed.
这又不是第一次有人让我失望
Wouldn't be the first time
someone's disappointed me.
好吧
Okay.
你看起来美极了
You look beautiful.
撒谎
Liar.
这里的人对你的照顾还周到么
So, you getting okay care here?
上乘毒品呢
Good drugs?
有什么需要的么
You need anything?
烟 沐浴露 还是锯子呢
Uh, cigarettes,
shampoo, hacksaw?
衣服
Clothes.
我的都一团糟了
Mine are a mess.
我下次来给你带些
I'll bring by some stuff.
我真的毁了感恩节
I really screwed
up Thanksgiving.
没有 没什么大不了的
No, it was no big deal.
孩子们呢
The kids?
我一定将他们吓坏了
I must have scared
the shit out of them.
他们很好
They're good.
我们昨晚已经谈过了
We, uh, talked
it out last night,
我昨晚哄他们睡觉 他们今天好多了
and I tucked them in,
they're fine today.
你没有让他们饱吃一顿
You didn't tuck them in.
不管怎样 我给最小的那一个读了会儿书
I read books to them,
the little ones, anyway.
你很快就会出来的
You'll be out soon.
你将会找回自己的
You'll see for yourself.
不会太快
Not soon.
72个小时
72 hours.
你已经安稳的度过了15个小时
You already got
15 under your belt.
我注册了60多天
I signed myself in
for 60 more days.
这是我自愿的
Voluntary commitment.
那就告诉他们你改变主意了
Well, tell them
you changed your mind.
我不能
I can't.
那是协议的一部分
That's part of the deal.
frank 我需要让自己变得正常
Frank, I got to
get myself normal.
我不能一直那样的伤害他们
I can't keep doing this to them.
你只是有点忧郁
You're just a little blue.
每个人偶尔都会发生这种事儿
It happens to everyone
every now and again.
我可以在家照顾你
I can take care of you at home.
不 你不能
No, you can't.
我爱你
I love you.
你属于我们
You belong with us.
我是
I'm...
我需要待在这个地方 真的
I'm where I need to be, okay?
我得走了
I got to go.
我参加了一个小组
I got group.
我能来点可卡因么
Can I borrow a cup of cocaine?
-都用完了
-咖啡呢
All out.
Coffee?
今天早上几个小的还好么
How are the little
ones this morning?
看过他们的母亲割腕之后么
After seeing their mother
slit her wrists?
受到了精神创伤
Traumatized.
应该支持为了那些看过这样鬼事情的孩子的组织
Has to be support groups for
kids who've seen shit like that.
是啊  在他们摧毁他们一半的同学之后
Yeah, in maximum
security prisons
关进一个最大限度保证安全的监狱
after they've mowed down
half their classmates.
你让steve过夜了么
You let Steve spend the night?
你指jimmy么
You mean Jimmy?
草了 我要叫他steve
Fuck that, I'm
calling him Steve.
我对他发出了一个请求
I sent him out on a quest.
让他重新赢回少女之心么
Mm! Making him re-win
the heart of the virgin?
天啊 V
Christ, V,
我不能让他再次的回到如此疯狂的境地
I can't let him
back into this madness.
那不是他自己的决定么
Isn't that his choice?
他现在觉得是想这么着
Well, he thinks
he wants it now,
但一两年之后呢
but just wait a year or two.
我怀着孕，Frank晚上在我们床上吐着
When I have one in the oven
and Frank throws up in our bed
Monica准备在
in the middle of the
night or Monica tries
柜橱里用旧袜子上吊自杀
to hang herself in a closet
with an old shoelace.
他只是个大男孩罢了，做这些决定还太早
He's a big boy, he can
make his own decisions.
嗨 Carl
Hey, Carl.
睡得好么
Sleep okay?
你觉得呢
What do you think?
哦么？
FIONA:
You hungry?
-给你做个三明治吧
-好
Let me make you a sandwich.
CARL: Okay.
伤残补助
Disability check
不会一个月来两次的 Frank
doesn't come
for another week, Frank.
我今早去医院看你妈了
I went to visit your mother
in the hospital this morning.
我们得把她整出来
We have to get
her out of there.
她在那挺好的
Best place for her.
-她很脆弱
-她已经崩溃了
She's fragile.
She's broken.
他们想把她变成普通人
They want to make her normal.
他们想帮她
They want to help her.
他们说的一般是什么意思？无聊，平凡
By which they mean average,
boring, medicated,
无聊，平凡，这对我的娇妻Monica来说多么残忍
a Stepford Monica.
她昨晚自杀未遂
She tried to kill herself
last night;
平庸对她来说不是坏事
boring would be a blessing.
他们会切她的脑叶
They perform lobotomies now.
不，不会的
No, they don't.
-刺激疗法
-没有
Shock treatment?
No.
我觉得他们会像莱雅公主那么干（星球大战的Leia）
Actually, I think they do.
Princess Leia did it.
10万伏特电击
100,000 volts of electricity
直达脑内
zapped into her skull!
电量多到我们全城停电
Draws so much power,
it takes out entire city blocks.
就是因为那些倒霉鬼的脑子正在被炸透
When our lights dim,
some poor fucker's
所以有时候我们的灯才那么暗
getting his brains fried.
别听他的，Carl
Don't listen to him, Carl.
吃你的饭
Eat your breakfast.
lobotomy是什么？（脑叶手术）
What's a lobotomy?
整个螺丝到你脑袋里
They jam a screwdriver
然后让你脑袋听话
into your head
and scramble your brains.
不可能的 天啊 Frank
No, they don't. Jesus, Frank.
-他们就是这么干的
-他们会让妈妈回来的
Yeah, they do!
They're gonna put Mom
而且她会变得更好的
back on her me.
They're gonna make her better.
那些药不会让她变好的
She's not better on her meds.
她成了行尸走肉 她放弃了她生命中所有的热爱
She's a zombie. She gives up
everything she loves in life.
是啊 都有什么啊 毒药 酒 还是你
Yeah, like what?
Drugs, alcohol, you?
我们
Us.
我会把她带出来的
I'm gonna bust her out of there
在他们把她变得不是她之前
before they steal what
makes Monica Monica.
你会帮我么
Are you with me?
别管她了 Frank
Leave her alone, Frank.
她需要个转机来变得更好
She needs a chance to get well.
你会让别人把你变得不像你么
Somebody can steal
what makes you you?
-不
-Carl你呢
No.
Carl?
他也不会帮你的
He's not helping you, either.
我能带着M-10么（枪名）
Can I bring my Mac-10 pistol?
别让他搅浑进来
把枪还给警察去
Leave him out of this.
The pistol's going back
你姐呢
to the cops.
Where's your sister?
洗澡呢
Shower.
-别去找Deb
-就去
Leave Debbie alone, Frank!
No.
出院之后 Monica会好起来的 C
Monica will be better when she
comes out of the hospital, Carl.
我通过了
I passed.
GED考试 我及格了
The GED-- I passed.
爸爸
(gasps)
Daddy!
你应该敲门的
Daddy, you're
supposed to knock!
你爱你妈么
Do you love your mother?
Cindy说这是为那些自己没有奶水的母亲
Cindy says they make this thing
for women who can't produce
准备的
their own milk.
你把这个挂在你的脖子上
You hang this doohickey
around your neck,
然后把这个贴在
and then you tape these
right over
你的乳头上
your nipples.
就好像是母乳喂养了
And the baby
can still breast-feed.
没事的 亲爱的 我来就行了
It's okay, honey,
I-I can do it.
不 他得和我们俩都亲近
No, it's important
for both of us to bond with him.
好吧
Okay.
来 小宝贝
There, sweet boy.
哇啊
Whoa.
哇哦
Wow.
真是
That's... Whoa.
哇啊
Whoa!
现在我知道这是怎么一回事了
Now I know what
all the fuss is about.
哦 来人了
Someone's here.
Oh.
妈
Mom?
Mom.
宝贝
Sweetie!
天啊 现在就能回家了
My goodness! Home already?
医院同意你走了么
Did the hospital let you leave?
它在哪
Where is it?
我还以为他们至少要让你们在那住一天
Thought they usually
like to keep you
它在哪
for at least a day.
Where is it, Mom?
什么在哪
Where's what, honey?
它
It.
我昨晚拼命生了六个小时
The baby that shoved
its ginormous head
才生出来的那个婴儿
out of my cooter for six
endless hours last night.
哦 天啊 医院给弄丢了
Oh, my. Did they lose it?
医院给我看了监控录下 就是你拿的
They showed me the video footage
of you taking it.
-哦 那个孩子
-医院本来要报警
Oh, that baby.
They were gonna call
我说不用了
the police, but I said no.
它在哪
Where is it?
-在哪
-烘干机里
Now, Mom!
In the dryer.
拿出来
Take it out.
他可能在睡觉
I think he's napping.
把它拿出来
Take it out!
我不想碰它
I don't want to touch it!
你在漏东西
You're leaking.
看他多可爱
Isn't he beautiful?
把它送回医院
Take it back to the hospital.
会有人要它的
Somebody will want it.
我就想要
I want it.
你不行
Well, you can't have it.
他这么可爱
He's such a sweet boy.
连哭都不哭
He never cries.
长得也漂亮
He's so handsome.
我们想给他起名叫Hiram
We want to name him Hiram
以你的外祖父的名字命名
after your grandfather.
或者叫明 保留他的中华血统
Or maybe Ming, to keep him
wired into his Chinese-ness.
闭嘴 Jody
Shut up, Jody.
它会回到医院的
It's going back.
K 求你了 别这样
Karen, please don't do this.
他们会把它送给脑残家庭或者其他什么的
They'll give it to the retarded
freaks' home or whatever.
他是我的外孙
He's my grandson.
我不会让你抛弃他的
I won't let you throw him away
就像扔掉废纸巾一样
like used Kleenex.
K 你妈说的对
You know, Karen, your
mom might be right.
或许可以让她先照顾一阵子
Maybe she should keep
him for a while.
谁知道
You know, who knows
社区服务会怎么对他
what social services is
going to do with him?
给我滚 L
Butt out, Lip!
你在这干嘛
What are you even doing here?
他又不是你孩子
He's not even yours.
这他妈又不是你孩子
This is none of your
goddamn business.
Tim W或着不管谁是他爹 你至少都该打个电话
At least call Tim Wong
or whoever the father is
告诉他这件事情
and tell him about it.
滚
Get out!
你这下子可不用当一个
You dodged a fucking RPG
无关紧要用过就扔的路人了
getting tossed over
by this one.
我已经知道了 哥们
Don't I know it, man.
把它送回医院
Take it back to the hospital.
(door opens and closes)
如果医院不收呢
What if they won't
take it back?
那就找个篮子扔里面
Then drop it in a basket
然后放到消防局门口
and leave it at
the fire station.
我无所谓
I don't give a shit.
不
SHEILA:
No.
决不
就这样
Yes!
他会和我在一起
He is staying with me.
那好
Fine!
我会报警的
Then I'm calling the police.
L在么
Lip here?
Lip!
你姐来了
It's your sister.
额
So...
你怎么找到我的
How'd you find me?
Jimmy.
K怎么样了
How's Karen?
就是一个贱人
Girl's a fucking bitch.
我表哥 Eli
My cousin, Eli, was born
他出生时 膝盖那还多了一条腿
with a foot coming out
of his knee.
现在他成了一个铁匠
Now he's a blacksmith.
唯一一个
Only one who can
pump the bellows
不用手就能拉风箱的铁匠
without using his hands.
我通过GED考试了
I passed my GED.
你看起来一点也不惊讶
Don't look so surprised.
嗯 我确实不惊讶
No, I'm not.
这个 额 很好
That's, um...
that's great.
那 之前我们有约定的
So... deal's a deal.
啊 太晚了
Ah, too late.
-覆水难收
-我通过了
Spilt milk.
I passed.
-你就回去上学
-木已成舟
You go back to school.
Water under the bridge.
少跟我废话
Knock off the clichés.
我已经做出了自己的选择
Road not taken.
我想要你回家 L
I want you home, Lip.
我们都想
We all do.
这样吧
Right.
冷水浇你 不让你睡觉
FRANK: It's cold water and
sleep deprivation.
让你站一整天
Make you stand all day
电你私处
with electrodes tied
to your genitals.
你把库克县当成阿布格莱布了吧（06年美军虐囚案发地 伊拉克）
I think you're mistaking
Cook County for Abi Grabie.
Abu Gradie.
Abu Ghraib.
我在巴士拉还参观过
Did a tour with the
Guard-- Basra.
他们一样都不会干的 Frank
They don't do any
of that, Frank.
我去年还在里面呆过
I was in there last year
因为我意外吸过量了
after my accidental overdose.
意外 你吸了可卡因之后把自己点着了
Accidental? You set yourself
on fire freebasing.
我们就是围个圈
It was mostly us
sitting in a circle
然后聊自己的家庭怎么乱七八糟的坑了自己
in a group talking
about how your family
M会拿Frank说事
screwed you up.
KEVIN: Oh, Monica talking about Frank?
那要说好大一阵子
That ought to take a while.
Frank 你有钱么
Frank, you got any cash?
零钱 大票
Moolah? Green?
我一定要把她从那里面弄出来
I got to spring her
out of there.
她是阴 我是阳
She's the yin to my yang.
她是我苏打水里面的威士忌
She's the scotch in my soda.
我俩是F和G（银幕上的一对舞蹈组合）
We are Fred and Ginger.
J和Y（Beatles的John和他老婆）M和M（米老鼠夫妇）
John and Yoko.
Mickey and Minnie.
更像是S和R（白老虎秀的两位主角 都是男的）
More like Siegfried and Roy.
A和E（希特勒和伊娃）
Adolf and Eva.
(laughter)
你孩子晚上还在医院干活么 T
Your boy still working nights
at the hospital, Tommy?
是啊 设备维修
Support services
technician, yeah.
设备维修 我还以为他是看门的呢
Support services technician?
I thought he was a janitor.
工作就是工作
A job's a job.
至少P找到了一个
At least Pat's got one.
P什么时候上班
What time's Patty go to work?
我们今晚去
We're on for tonight.
-今晚干什么
-和我家里人吃饭
What's tonight?
Dinner with my family.
你问过我 所以我就安排了
You asked, you got it.
他们过来
Are they coming here?
额 不是
Uh... no.
我爸从84年BJ在科米斯基公园的演唱会后
Dad hasn't been south
of the Art Institute Gala
就没来过城南了
since Billy Joel
played Comiskey Park in '84.
-那去你家吃饭
-也不是
Going to their house for dinner?
Nope.
啊，她肯定会先让你去抓跳蚤再来我家
Uh, Mom would have
to have you deloused first.
她有重度洁癖
She's a germophobe.
如果你想从盘子里拿出来个杏仁
You want an almond
out of the serving dish,
那就应该带着外壳手套用手术钳子来
you have to wear
surgical gloves and use tongs.
我见过你妈
I met your mom.
她挺好的
She's... she's cool.
你见过他妈
You met his mom?
Candace.
肉毒杆菌打的有点多
A little heavy on the Botox
还有香奈儿5号 不过还好
and Chanel No. 5,
but nice.
那我们去哪
So where are we meeting?
M饭店，市中心
Uh, Morton's, downtown.
我爸在那有一个酒柜
Dad has a wine locker there.
一个黄铜的小牌子
Little brass plaque
上面有他的名字好好所有的细节
with his name on
it and everything.
-每个人都被邀请了
-嗯 老爸结帐
Everybody invited?
Yep. Dad's buying,
所以点菜单上最贵的呗
so order the most
expensive thing
顶级牛排
on the menu.
Prime rib?
-没问题
-带骨上等牛腰排
Sure.
Bone-in porterhouse steak?
什么都行 Deb 你呢 免费晚餐哦
Anything you want. What do
you say, Debs, free meal?
去不成 J 有事要忙
No can do, Jim. Busy.
-干什么
-在HH家过夜
Doing what?
Sleeping over at Holly Herkimier's.
什么也别跟她学
Don't do anything she does.
大号龙虾
Big-ass lobster?
你猜行不行
You bet.
♪ Bad, bad heart ♪
♪ Bad, bad mind ♪
♪ Thinking bad thoughts ♪
♪ All the time ♪
♪ Waking up in the morning... ♪
老天
Jesus Christ!
你从来没洗过啊
Don't you ever hose
these things out?
比一个死妓女的屁股还难闻
Smells worse than
a dead hooker's ass in there.
小声点 好吧
Keep your voice
down, all right?
别担心 牛仔
Easy, cowboy.
那个桔色的一般人可不行
That orange one's
for experts only.
如果你被逮住了
Hey, you do get caught,
和我没有任何关系 行吧
you never heard
of me, all right?
里面怎么样 小可爱
Doing good in there, pumpkin?
还成吧 爸爸
A-okay, Daddy.
-警察
-啊
Cops!
Aah!
-快点 妈妈 动起来
-好的
Come on, Mom. Hurry up.
Okay.
-我没闲着 好的
-妈 快啊
I'm hurrying. Okay!
Mom, come on!
警察来了 妈妈
Police are here, Mom.
你好 J女士
TONY:
Hello, Mrs. Jackson.
嘿
Hey.
T 你妈妈最近怎么样
Tony. How's your mom?
糖尿病还在发作么
The diabetes still giving her fits?
Yes, ma'am.
夏天掉了两个脚趾头 但她撑了过来
Lost two toes over the summer,
but she's hanging tough.
这也是没办法的事情
Well, she'd
have to be--
毕竟她和冰上舞蹈团一起滑了这么多年
all those years skating
with the Ice Capades.
额 有人报警说说有一起绑架
Uh... we got a call
about a kidnapping.
-哦
-妈妈和Jody
Oh...
Mom and Jody
从医院里偷走了我的孩子
stole my baby from
the hospital.
你有孩子了
You had your baby?
恭喜你啊
Congratulations.
谢谢 但那他妈其实是一个吓人的表演
Thanks. It was a fucking
horror show, but I...
我最终还是把它弄出来了
finally had the damn thing.
他们从医院把它偷了 我想让你把它带回去
They stole it, and I want
you to take it back.
你不想要这个孩子
You don't... want
to keep the baby?
是个智障
It's retarded.
我想把它送回去 然后医院可以把它
I want it to go back
so they can give it away
送到那些愿意收留唐氏综合症患儿的地方
to the Down Syndrome
baby do-gooders
或者乡下哪里
or the county or whatever.
唐氏综合症婴儿准确的说法是
Correct term for Downs kids
发育迟缓症
is "developmentally
delayed."
我孩子被我妈
Well, my baby was
stolen by my mom
和她发育迟缓的男友偷了
and her developmentally
delayed boyfriend.
-他不是我男友
-我不是
He's not my boyfriend.
I'm not?
啊 J女士
TONY:
Uh, Mrs. Jackson,
你是不是拿走了你女儿的孩子
did you take
your daughter's baby?
孩子 什么孩子
Baby? What baby?
就是洗衣篮的那个孩子
Ma'am, is the baby
in the laundry basket?
是
Yes.
把它交给警察 妈
Give it to the cop, Mom.
K 宝贝 求你了 别这样做
Karen, honey, please
don't do this.
啊 天啊
OFFICER:
Ah, man.
瞧瞧你多可爱啊
Look how handsome you are.
多帅啊 真好看
Yes, you are.
妈 把他交给警察
Give it to the damn cop, Mom!
这么说 这位是你的母亲
So this is your mother,
然后她想照看这个婴儿
and she wants
to take care of the baby?
对 但是我不想要
Yes, but I don't
-它留在这
-哦
want it here.
Oh.
你想让一个陌生人照看他
And you want a total stranger
还是让伊利诺州政府
to take him or the
State of Illinois
用纳税人的钱
to be responsible for him
为他负责
on the taxpayers' dime?
饿了么
You hungry?
我想去吃泰国菜
I'm thinking Thai.
Yeah.
就这样 你就这么走了
That's it?
You're just gonna leave?
Jackson夫人 很高兴见到您
Nice seeing you, Mrs. Jackson.
-我会替您问候我母亲的
-谢谢
I'll tell Mom you asked after her.
(whispers): Please.
妈 你是要我还是要这个孩子
It's either me
or that baby, Mom.
你决定吧
Your choice.
我觉得应该就是这里了
I think this must be the place.
我能出来了么 这里边好热
Can I get out?
It's hot in here.
-不行
-Ow
No.
Ow!
Monica?
如果你希望 我也可以是Monica
I can be if you want me to be.
天啊
(hushed):
Jesus!
Monica?
Kermit?
Frank?
你的脑袋怎么了
What'd you do to your head?
哦 这是我治疗的一部分
Oh, um, my therapy.
帮助我舒缓神经
It calms my nerves.
他们在你头上做电疗了
You let 'em zap your head?
有助于控制病情发作
Helps with my seizures.
天啊
Jesus.
Frank 你应该尝试一下再否决 很安逸的
Try it before you knock it,
Frank. Very restful.
你有看到过Monica么
Have you seen Monica around?
Yeah, um...
在走廊对面的左手边
across the hall on your left.
Monica?
Hey, Monica?
Frank.
我来带你出去
I came to get you out.
我告诉过你我不想出去
I told you I don't want out.
为什么停下
WOMAN:
Why'd you stop?
你高潮了
Did you come?
Um...
Frank,
这位是Jill
this is Jill.
Jill这个是我的丈夫Frank
Jill this is my husband, Frank.
妈
Mom?
Fiona快看啊
Fiona! Fiona, look!
童趣
Boys.
Carl...
对不起
Sorry. We don't let him out
我们不经常带他出来
of his cage very often.
Carl!
carl 过来
Get over here.
对了 Jim你最近都在忙些什么
So, Jim, what have
you been up to?
还在寻找创新思路
Still finding new
来激发潜能
and creative ways
to underachieve?
最近我周游南美洲
I was traveling around
South America till recently.
你还在帮父亲处理所有痔疮手术的事情
Are you still handling all the
hemorrhoidectomies for Dad?
Chip刚从父亲的外科医师那里接手工作
Chip just joined Dad's practice
after his surgical residency,
继续这项伟大的工程
following in
the great man's footsteps.
这么说你会在人身体内动刀子
So you get to cut into people?
帅呆了
Awesome.
他带你去滑雪了么
He take you skiing yet?
还没
Uh, no.
我在这方面的唯一特长就是
My only talent involving snow
is knowing how
在我父亲在过道熟睡的时候把积雪清走而不惊醒他
to shovel the walk without
disturbing my father sleeping on it.
而Carl最擅长的就是在雪地上撒尿
And Carl's pretty good
at peeing in it as well.
他有年新年带去圣摩里兹度假的(滑雪胜地)
What was the name
of that girl that he took
那女孩叫什么来着 Chrissie
to St. Moritz
on New Year's? Chrissie?
Lizzie 还是别的 我记得她名字的结尾有个ie
Lizzie? Something. I remember it
had "ie" on the end of it.
当时我才17
I was 17.
你高中的时候就带女朋友去欧洲
You took a girlfriend to Europe
in high school?
我爸买的机票
Dad offered a ticket.
他带着那个女孩一路来到阿尔卑斯山
He drags her all
the way to the Alps,
然后把她丢在那里的酒店
then leaves her in
the hotel room sitting there
因为在缆车上新认识了个法国姑娘
for some French girl
he met on the gondola.
Chip放过你弟弟吧
Chip, leave your brother alone.
有两件事你可以指望的
Two things you can count on:
一是妈妈明显偏袒她的小儿子
Mom's naked favoritism
for her youngest...
根本没有
CANDACE:
That's not true.
我哥哥还认为我是个不敢还击的侏儒
My brother still thinks of me as
the runt that didn't punch back.
她的小儿子骗了她一万刀之后
...and her youngest's quick
and stealthy exit
就迅速消失的无影无踪
after he weasels her
out of another ten grand.
这次我打算要2万刀了
I was hoping to milk her for
another 20 this time.
正如你的名字Chip
With a name like Chip,
you'd think you'd want
你想挑战一下刻板的形象
to defy the stereotype.
-Fiona别 我不在乎的
Fiona, don't.
It's fine.
不 不行
No, it's not.
对不起 我迟到了
Well, sorry to be late.
有一个癌症晚期病人的手术
Whipple on
a stage-four patient.
这么说 你就是那位神秘的Fiona
So, you are
the mysterious Fiona.
这位是Fiona的弟弟Carl
And these are
Fiona's brothers, Carl...
还有Ian
and Ian...
见到你很高兴Ian
Well, nice to meet you, Ian.
我们点餐了么
Have we ordered?
失陪一下
Excuse me.
去下洗手间
Bathroom.
-先生 您的水
-谢谢
And your drink, sir.
Thank you.
你知道的 我得去洗下手
Ah, you know,
I gotta wash my hands.
给我一份生菜沙拉和海鲈鱼
I'll have the iceberg lettuce
salad and the sea bass.
48盎司上等肋排 双切
Double-cut,
48-ounce prime rib,
五分熟
medium-rare,
还有2磅重的缅因州龙虾 谢谢
and the two-pound
Maine lobster, please.
Hey.
他们知道你是同性恋么
Do they know you're gay?
我不是
I'm not gay.
开玩笑 那么这是什么
Really?
What's this then?
你真的想知道
Honestly?
这一切的一切 就是我
Anything that walks, that's me.
天呐 Moni又一个女人
Jesus, Moni, another lady?
你知道的 我会觉得孤独
(sighs) You know,
I get lonely.
你爱她么
Do you love her?
我刚认识她
I just met her.
你们在这儿干什么
What are you doing here?
我们来救你出去
We came to break you out.
我跟你说过了 我不想出去
I told you, I don't want out.
好吧 该死的 我想出去
Oh, hell, I do.
Jill 没人问你意见
No one's offering, Jill.
但是你为什么把Debbie带来
And why did you have to
drag Debbie into this?
我不觉得我单独来你会跟我走
I didn't think you'd come
if it was just me.
她在这做什么
What is she in for?
做精神评估
Psych evaluation to see
看是否能接受审判
if I'm competent
to stand trial.
你做了什么
What'd you do?
对我丈夫开了26枪
Shot my husband 26 times.
天啊 你用的什么 AK
Jesus, what'd you use, an AK?
手枪
Pistol.
我上了两次子弹才够
I reloaded... twice.
(laughs)
Moni我们希望你和家人在一起
Moni, we want you with us.
孩子们需要你
The kids need you.
我需要你
I need you.
还疼么
Does it hurt?
不疼了
No, I'm okay.
宝贝 很抱歉让你目睹了那一幕
I'm sorry you had
to see that, honey.
我当时很低落 你知道么
I was just so low, you know?
yeah.
不过我现在好了
But I'm okay now.
所以
So...
这次你带我们冲出去的宏伟计划是什么
What's this grand plan you have
for busting us out?
明白了
Got it.
唉 不够长
Whoa. That's short.
距离地面还有很远
That's a long way down.
可以把床单绑在一头
Could tie sheets to the end.
什么
What?!
从john的窗户外
Hey, it's only two stories down
to the roof...
下到车顶只有2层楼
outside the ladies' john.
需要我去接Liam么
You want me to go pick up Liam?
嗯 V可以留他过夜的
Uh, V will be okay keeping him
overnight.
不错的餐厅 Jimmy看啊
Great restaurant,
Jimmy. Check out
我偷了一把很帅的小刀
this cool knife I stole.
这个要还回去
That's going back.
哎 他们有成吨的小刀 是不可能发现的
Hey, they won't miss it.
They got tons of 'em.
给我拿来 现在去睡觉
Give me that.
Bed, now.
嘿 禁止动我剩下的龙虾
Hey, nobody touch
my leftover lobster.
明早 我想把他加进我的烤肉桂松饼里
I want to put it in my cinnamon
toaster waffle in the morning.
Hey, Fiona.
Jimmy的父亲Lloyd
Jimmy's dad Lloyd,
他 他
he, uh..
晚安
Good night.
安
Night.
怎么了
What?
我爱你
I love you.
你会离开么
Are you gonna leave?
不会
No.
人总是会离去的
Everybody always leaves.
我不会
I won't.
耐心点
Patience...
别这样
Stop that!
ESTEFANIA:
Steve!
Estefania...
天啊
Jesus!
-嘿 嘿 嘿 Estefania
-是谁啊
Hey, hey, hey, Estefania.
what is it?
Estefania 嘿 冷静一下
Estefania, hey,
calm down, calm down.
发生了什么
What the hell happened?
是 marco hey marco
Marco...
Hey...
等下 这是Marco干的 他打你了么
Wait. Marco did this to you?
He hit you?
Marco打你了么
Did Marco hit you?
你是我丈夫
You my husband...
帮帮我好吗
Help me, please?
求求你帮帮我
Please help me!
好吗
Please?
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
睡不着 想抽一口
Uh, I couldn't sleep.
Needed a smoke.
你不必在外面抽
You don't have to do it out here.
我爸回来后 整个家就像个烟灰缸
With Dad home,
the whole house is an ashtray.
天啦 冻死了
Christ, it's freezing.
是因为Karen么
Karen?
恩
Yeah.
我不知道
I don't know.
可能吧 我 我也不知道
Maybe. I-I don't know.
我不明白一个人有个孩子
I don't get how you have a kid
但是怎么却能完全不关心他
and not give a shit
what happens to it.
不管它是低能 或者有两个头
Retarded, two heads,
没有脸  不管怎样--那还是你的孩子
no face, whatever--
it's still you.
没有脸
No face?
恩 对 可能它一定得有张脸吧
Yeah, well, maybe it would
have to have a face.
你应该回家去
You should go home.
你要赶我走了
Oh, you kicking me out?
回房子里去吧
Get your ass back in the house
别想太多了
and stop thinking so much.
你想再做一次么
You want to fuck again?
现在不来 几分钟之后我就睡觉
I'm only gonna be up
a couple more minutes.
嘿 伙计们
Hey, pal.
嘿 兄弟 伙计
-有火机吗
-你什么时候能戒烟啊
Got a light? when are you gonna give those up？
小心抽死你
they are gonna kill you
我知道
I know.
我下次试试催眠我自己
I'm gonna try hypnosis next.
我没有 对不起啦
Uh, no, don't.
No, sorry.
你的胸牌呢
Where's your I.D. badge?
落在我抽屉里了
Oh, left it in my locker.
还没到换班时间呢
Shift's not over.
我把我的吸入器
Left my inhaler...
落在车里了
...in the car.
我有结核和哮喘 非常严重
Tuberculosis and
asthma. Horrible.
Chuck，七区有麻烦了
Chuck, we got trouble on seven.
-精神病区
-收到
Psych unit.
Roger that.
当你在医院时
Got to keep your I.D. badge visible
记得一直把你的胸牌放在显眼的地方
at all times
on hospital grounds.
Debbie!
快上车
Get in the car.
Debbie 快上车
Debbie, get in the car.
快上车
Get in the car.
Debs,快上车
Debs, get in the car!
快上车啊
Get in the car!
我爱你 Debbie
I love you, Debbie!
Debbie 我爱你
Debbie, I love you!
她说我们没有她会更好
She said we're better
off without her.
这场考试总计两个小时
TEACHER: You will have two
hours for this exam.
这是选择题
This is multiple choice.
如果你想改答案 你确认
If you change an answer,
be sure to fully erase
你把上一个答案擦干净并且把第二个答案写清楚
your first answer and
clearly circle your second.
我是不会
I am not...
我不会读心术
I am not a mind reader.
如果你不知道答案的话 接着做后面的然后再回过来
If you do not know an answer,
move on and come back to...
你要去哪
Where you going?
离这越远越好
Anywhere far the fuck
away from here.
我今天回学校了
Hey, I went back
to school today.
参加了物理期末考试
Took the AP Physics final.
你都没去上过课
You haven't even
been going to class.
我几年前就把那本书读完了
I read the book a couple years ago.
妈 就这样
This is it, Mom.
最后一次机会
Last chance.
我没有开玩笑
I'm not kidding,
我要走了
I'm gone.
你选要我还是要宝宝
It's me or the baby.
你选吧
Decide.
不要这样
Please don't do this.
我还是宝宝
Me or the baby.
我选宝宝 亲爱的
The baby, sweetheart.
Karen!
你知道的 你一定会后悔的
You know, you're
going to regret this.
嗷呜 我记得你说过这些不痛的
Ow, ow, ow! I thought you said
these things didn't hurt!
我骗你的
CARL: I lied.
停手
Ow! Dude, knock it off.
Carl和Jimmy在客厅玩气枪
Carl's having an air soft war
with Jimmy in the living room.
他们又会在电视机上留个坑的
They're gonna put a dent
in the TV screen again.
出去玩 我已经跟你们说了两次了
Outside! I told you both
twice already!
-火鸡
-慢慢习惯吧
Turkey?
Get used to it.
Carl's Morton餐厅的剩菜
That and Carl's
Morton leftovers
是帮我们度过接下来两周难关的食物
are going to tide us over
for the next two weeks.
听着，我觉得
Listen, I kind of need to talk
我有点事要和你聊下
to you about something.
别担心她在这 她完全不懂英语
Don't worry about her.
She doesn't speak any English.
她现在住在这了吗
She living here now?
我的老天 我倒希望不是
Good Lord, I hope not.
你知道Jimmy的爸爸Lloyd
You know, Jimmy's dad Lloyd?
我 我觉得我们
I, uh, think we kind of...
我的天
Oh, Jesus.
我们破产了 Frank
We're broke, Frank.
自从你把我们的钱花光
I haven't hidden money in
there since you cleaned us out
我已经不把钱藏在那里了
last May.
钱在哪
Where is it?
我们没钱了
There is no money.
不 这些是我的
Whoa! No. Those are mine.
别这样 让他走吧 Ian
Come on, let him go, Ian.
不 把它放回去
No, put it back!
什么 你在搞笑吗
What, are you
fucking kidding me?
-小心
-离我远点
Hey! Hey! Watch it!
Get off of me!
-住手
-你在扯淡吗
Hey, stop that!
Are you kidding me?!
听着 快点停手
Listen!
Fucking stop it!
停手
Knock it off!
你TM敢跟我这样 你个小
Don't you fuck with me!
You little...
打孩子和女人的男人都去死吧
♪ The evening sleeps away ♪
♪ Another day
has come and gone ♪
♪ The streetlights
soak the shade ♪
♪ Synthetic rays
replace the sun ♪
♪ Conscience soon dying ♪
♪ When you get what you want ♪
♪ Foresight goes and fades ♪
♪ In retrospect,
we'll figure out ♪
♪ The evening sleeps away ♪
♪ Realize the afterthought
of doubt ♪
♪ Well, these last couple days ♪
♪ Been why we're going there
and how ♪
Lip!
♪ For these three days on end ♪
♪ Got to be hopeful ♪
♪ These three days on end ♪
♪ Got to get up
and catch my second wind ♪
♪ Got to be up for it. ♪
不不能再来了
I can't again.
我要去睡觉
I got to sleep.
小家伙们早上还要上课呢
Kids have school
in the morning.
我得找个鞋盒子
I got to find a shoebox for...
把Debbie的艺术作品装起来
Debbie's art project.
Carl还没有做完他的拼写练习
Carl hasn't done his spelling.
Carl将会有一节卖烘烤食品的课
Carl's class is
having a bake sale.
我要去 我要去做一些小饼干
I got to--
I'm gonna make cookies.
小饼干 好吧
Cookies, right.
然后Liam要去诊所
And Liam has to go
to the clinic for...
进行他的下一次（预约检查）
for his next set...
去它的 过来点
Screw it, get up here.
♪ We will know
what it's all about ♪
♪ And today is the day ♪
Lip?
我好冷
I so cold.
你热么
You hot?
好的
Okay.
那当然了
Sure.
♪ And I want to say,
as I survey ♪
Oh.
♪ I'd like to take you
miles away ♪
♪ With me today ♪
【贴吧无耻之徒字幕组】
【翻译】折翼的鸟 NG 郭巍 oh ba ttle
【校对】dream NG 郭威 哎呦
♪ Sweet lover,
got nothing on me ♪
♪ You want it,
but you can't see ♪
♪ You want it, so just say so ♪
♪ One time, if you just let go ♪
♪ Baby, freedom's got
nothing on me ♪
♪ I'll give you
everything you need ♪
♪ Baby, give and take
is part of the game ♪
♪ Reacting like
it's one and the same ♪
♪ You thought you'd find
something on me ♪
♪ Slow down,
you got to slow down. ♪